planetayurveda.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy - Planet Ayurveda

This privacy policy is intended to inform you of www.planetayurveda.com policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that you share with us during your visit of this website. It does not apply to information collected by us, or on our behalf, in person, through the mails, by telephone or any other means. Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms shall have the meanings assigned to such terms in the Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement for the Site found at www.planetayurveda.com. If you have some comments, suggestions, questions, or concerns about Privacy Policy of www.planetayurveda.com, please contact us.

By visiting or registering on our Website, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

"Personal Information" is information about you that gives you personal identification like your name, state of residence, and e-mail address etc. By accessing our Site and/or registering on our Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to the Privacy Policy detailed here.

"Anonymous Information" is the information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information. Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons.

www.planetayurveda.com collects and uses Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy. www.planetayurveda.com is abide to not to resale any information about you and will not share all your information with any organization or the company.

Any and all uses of Personal Information by www.planetayurveda.com comply with applicable laws.

## HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?

When you communicate with us via our Site, www.planetayurveda.com collects your Personal Information only if you provide it to www.planetayurveda.com voluntarily. Portions of the Site may allow you to provide www.planetayurveda.com with Personal Information in order to deliver requested materials, products or services to you.

## INFORMATION WE TRACK

**You may give us your information by filling in forms on the Site or any Application or by corresponding with us by post, phone, email, on social media or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you:**

  * Register for an account with us (whether online or in-store);
  * Place an order;
  * Sign up to our newsletters;
  * Request marketing to be sent to you;
  * Contact our Customer Care Team;
  * Enter a competition, promotion or survey; or
  * Give us some feedback.

#### Log Files

Similar to many websites, www.planetayurveda.com gathers certain anonymous, non-personal information automatically and stores it in web server log files. This information includes:-

  * Internet protocol addresses
  * Browser type,
  * Internet service provider (ISP),
  * Site entry/exit pages,
  * Operating system,
  * Date/time stamp, and
  * Click stream data.

www.planetayurveda.com uses this information to improve our Site, analyze trends, administer the Site, track users movements around the Site, and gather aggregate information about the Site user base as a whole. Aggregate information is data www.planetayurveda.com collects about a group or category of services or Site visitors/users From which individual identities has been removed, and therefore does not include your Personal Information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a users computer for record-keeping purposes. It can also help www.planetayurveda.com understand how the Site visitors click to the Site, and what pages they view during their visit. Similar to many websites, www.planetayurveda.com uses a standard technology called a "session cookie" to enable the Site to recognize you during a visit to this Site. The session cookie is stored in temporary memory on your computer and is not retained after you close your browser.

You can set your web browser software to disable cookies. To do so, please refer to the help section of your specific browser for more information on how to manage or disable cookies. If you disable cookies, you may still view the Site, but some areas of our site may not work properly.

## PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We restrict access to the Personal Information we have collected From or about you, as described above, to those employees and officers of the organization KRISHNA HERBAL COMPANY who need to know the information to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard your Personal Information.

Despite our use of commercially reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Information From unauthorized access or disclosure, the internet is not an inherently secure environment and so we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information. We assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.

## USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We process personal information for the following services and purposes:

Account set up, Account management and order processing.

We use personal information such as your name, email address, phone number, card details, and information about your device to:

  1. To set up and administer your account
  2. To deliver your purchases
  3. To provide customer care and technical support
  4. To process returns
  5. For security and to verify your identity
  6. To take payment and process refunds
  7. Fraud protection
  8. To send you messages by email, SMS or otherwise such as order updates
  9. To provide you with marketing (where we have the right to do so – see marketing section below)
  10. To communicate with you

## USE OF ANONYMOUS INFORMATION

www.planetayurveda.com may create Anonymous Information records From Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name etc.) that makes the information personally identifiable to you. www.planetayurveda.com may use this Anonymous Information for any purpose in its discretion. Further, www.planetayurveda.com reserves the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to third parties for certain reasons.

## SHARING / DISLCOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Except as set out in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or giveaway any of your personalized information to third parties unless we have your express permission or are required by law to do so.

  1. Sharing Personal Information with partners and affiliates www.planetayurveda.com/ Krishna Herbal Company may share some or all of your Personal Information with Affiliates, in which case www.planetayurveda.com will require our Affiliates/partners to honor Privacy Policy of www.planetayurveda.com
  2. Sharing Personal Information in the event of Acquisition In the unlikely event that www.planetayurveda.com is acquired merges with another entity or sells portions of its assets; our databases (which may contain your online personal information) will be among transferred assets.
  3. Disclosing Personal Information to Comply with Laws and Similar Disclosure www.planetayurveda.com may disclose your Personal Information if it believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to:- 
    1. Comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on www.planetayurveda.com; or
    2. To protect and defend our rights or property, and/or the rights or property of the visitors/users of our Site, or third parties.

## YOUR RIGHTS

Under the General Data Protection Regulation, you, as a data subject have a number of rights which are detailed below. Some of these only apply in specific circumstances and are qualified in several respects by exemptions in data protection legislation. We will advise you in our response to your request if we are relying on any such exemptions.

### Right to access

You have the right to request information about the personal data we hold on you at any time. You can contact Planet Ayurveda and we will provide you with your personal data via e-mail. You should include adequate information to identify yourself and such other relevant information that will reasonably assist us in fulfilling your request.

### Right to rectification

You can request us to rectify and correct any personal data that we are processing about you which is incorrect. If you have a Planet Ayurveda account you can edit or delete your personal data in my account section under privacy setting.

### Right to portability

Whenever Planet Ayurveda processes your personal data, by automated means based on your consent or which was necessary for us to provide you with our products and services, you have the right to get a copy of your data transferred to you. This only includes the personal data you have submitted to us. You may have the right to have your personal data transferred by us directly to an other organisation, if this is technically feasible.

### Right to erasure

You have the right to erase any personal data processed by Planet Ayurveda at any time except for the following situations:

  1. You have an ongoing matter with Customer Service.
  2. You have an open order which has not yet been shipped or partially shipped.
  3. You have an unsettled debt with Planet Ayurveda, regardless of the payment method.
  4. If you are suspected or have misused our services within the last four years.
  5. If you have made any purchase, we will keep your personal data in connection to your transaction for book-keeping purposes.
  6. Your right to object to processing based on legitimate interest.
  7. You have the right to object to processing of your personal data that is based on Planet Ayurveda's legitimate interest. Where we suspend our processing of your personal data we will still be permitted to store your personal data, but any other processing of this information will require your consent, subject to certain exemptions. When you do so your account will cease to exit and you will be considered inactive.

### Right to withdraw consent

Where we have relied upon your consent to process your personal data, you have the right to withdraw that consent.

To opt out of marketing, you can use the unsubscribe link or the opt-out option found in the marketing communication you receive from us. For other marketing preferences, you can visit the **My Account** tab when you log into your account or the " **Contact Us** " option within the relevant Service.

## POSTING TO PUBLIC AREAS

Please note that if you post or make available your Personal Information in public areas of the Site, such as in blogs, such information may be collected and used by third parties over whom www.planetayurveda.com has no control. www.planetayurveda.com is not responsible for the use by such third parties of Personal Information you post or make available in public areas of the Site.

## ACCESS AND ACCURACY OF DATA

Upon your written request through email/fax or letter, we will allow you to review any of your Personal Information that you disclosed to us, except for any Personal Information that we collect in connection with or in anticipation of any claim or legal proceeding. If you discover any inaccuracy, please let us know so that we can make whatever corrections are appropriate. Before this process you will need to provide your Identity proof to us, so that someone else won't do it deliberately.

## DELETION OF DATA

We keep Personal Information for an unlimited time period. However you can ask us to delete your Personal Information From our marketing databases, and if you do that we will comply as soon as practicable. If you would like to submit revisions to your Personal Information, please do so on the website or you may send them via e-mail to [herbalremedies123@yahoo.com](mailto:herbalremedies123@yahoo.com). OR You can directly go to Privacy Settings under My Account and can delete your account. 

## AGE

www.planetayurveda.com does not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13. www.planetayurveda.com would be pleased to work with parents and guardians to delete From our records Personal Information a child may improperly disclose. If you believe that www.planetayurveda.com has collected Personal Information about a child who is under the age of 13, please contact us at [herbalremedies123@yahoo.com](mailto:herbalremedies123@yahoo.com) and such Personal Information will be deleted.

## OTHER WEB SITES

www.planetayurveda.com provision of links to other Web sites on the Site is for your convenience and does not signify www.planetayurveda.com endorsement of such other Web sites or their contents. Links to other Web sites may also be posted by other visitors to this Site on the blog available on the Site. Planet Ayurveda has no control over, does not review, and cannot be responsible for these third party Web sites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these third party Web sites. We cannot control how third parties may use Personal Information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third-party web site you visit before using it or disclosing your Personal Information to it.

## SECURITY

www.planetayurveda.com uses reasonable measures to maintain the security of your Personal Information. However, no company, including www.planetayurveda.com, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

## NOTICE FOR VISITORS

You should be aware that the privacy regulations are not harmonized across the world. Because www.planetayurveda.com is located in India the Privacy Policy has been created to satisfy Government of India regulations. By using the Site, you agree to the level of privacy protection set out in our Privacy Policy irrespective of your country of residence or use.

## PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision and changes will be posted on this page. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated on this page. You are urged to return to check the Privacy Policy for the latest updates prior to submitting any Personal Information through the Site.

This Privacy Policy was created in June 2018
